I got one more for you.
Okay.
This one has a working title.
It would either be something like the flip the bill bill or the you are the father bill.
And what this would entail is that the constituencies where Roe v. Wade has been repealed
would be supported fiscally by the Republicans who passed the bills.
So, you know, for the women who are forced to have children that don't have a father present,
their actual representative would be on the birth certificate and foot in the bill for the baby.
Yeah.
You think I can get some support?
I mean, I think that is probably your best bill idea so far.
I like it.
That would be the fastest way to get abortion legal in this country.
Just don't make us the baby daddies of your children.
That's it.
So why is it so hard for bills to get passed?
What even is the process?
I don't think regular people know.
Oh, that was another way inside.
That came with you from overseas.
Very instilled in me.
I mean, the process is that you, you know, obviously have a conversation like this, come
up with a bill idea, draft the bill, introduce it, get people to co-sign, and then hopefully
get it submitted to a committee, have a hearing, passes it out of the committee, and then,
you know, work, leadership, and try to get it to be on the floor to be voted on.
The problem right now, and why we can't pass things, is that you have a whip for the Republican
Party, that's in leadership, that don't know how to whip, and you have a majority leader that
is supposed to control the floor that doesn't know how to control the floor, and then you
have a leader in this speaker who doesn't know how to lead.
So we essentially are just like, hanging out, watching the clock, being like, are there
bills to be voted on?
Mm-hmm.
Do you know how to pass a bill?
Yeah.
I mean, there are less steps to the cha-cha slide.
And that's just the House side.
So everything Ilhan just explained is the House side.
Then you've got to figure out what's going on in the Senate side.
If we, Democrats, had control of all three off Republicans, then some bills would be passed,
but with this divided government and horrible leadership from the Republicans, it's hard.
I thought Hollywood was messy.
This sounds like a real shitstorm on a daily basis.
Yeah.